Contact

ronjack2121@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ron-harrisbsn-rn-cmsrn-a3aa0a103 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing
Healthcare Management
Healthcare

Ron Harris, BSN, RN, CMSRN

Staff RN at MD Anderson Cancer Center

Pearland, Texas

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Customer Service, Patient Safety, Healthcare Information Technology (HIT), Electronic Medical Record (EMR), and Nursing. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor of Applied Science - BASc focused in Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse from The University of Texas at Arlington.

Experience

MD Anderson Cancer Center
Staff RN
January 2013 - Present (7 years 6 months)

St.LukesHealth

Nurse

September 2004 - January 2013 (8 years 5 months)

Education

The University of Texas at Arlington

Bachelor of Applied Science - BASc, Registered Nursing/Registered

Nurse · (2016 - 2016)